<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="core/rss.xsl" type="text/xsl" media="screen"?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
	
<atom:link href="http://www.fosterandpartners.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


<title>Foster + Partners</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com</link>
<description>Latest news from Foster + Partners</description>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013</lastBuildDate>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Lee Hallman joins Foster + Partners to head up Interiors Group</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/lee-hallman-joins-foster-+-partners-to-head-up-interiors-group/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/lee-hallman-joins-foster-+-partners-to-head-up-interiors-group/</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013</pubDate>
<description>Foster + Partners has further strengthened its in-house capabilities by hiring Lee Hallman, previously Head of Design at Candy &amp; Candy, and two of his former Design Directors, to lead the practice’s Interiors Group.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Architectural Association Foster + Partners Prize</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/the-architectural-association-foster-+-partners-prize/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/the-architectural-association-foster-+-partners-prize/</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013</pubDate>
<description>The Architectural Association and Foster + Partners are pleased to announce the award of the 2013 Foster + Partners Prize, which is presented annually to the AA Diploma student whose portfolio best addresses the themes of sustainability and infrastructure. The recipient is selected jointly by the AA and Foster + Partners at the end of each academic year.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Official opening of The Bow, Calgary's tallest tower</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/official-opening-of-the-bow-calgarys-tallest-tower/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/official-opening-of-the-bow-calgarys-tallest-tower/</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013</pubDate>
<description>Special events have been held in Calgary this week to mark the official opening of The Bow, a 237-metre-high headquarters tower – the city’s tallest building and Canada’s tallest tower outside Toronto.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Winner of the seventh RIBA Norman Foster Travelling Scholarship announced</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/winner-of-the-seventh-riba-norman-foster-travelling-scholarship-announced/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/winner-of-the-seventh-riba-norman-foster-travelling-scholarship-announced/</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013</pubDate>
<description>The 2013 RIBA Norman Foster Travelling Scholarship has been awarded to Sigita Burbulyte of Bath School of Architecture for her proposal, ‘Charles Booth Going Abroad’. She will be granted £6,000 to develop her research study, which takes the poverty maps of Victorian social reformer Charles Booth as the starting point for an exploration of slum communities across four continents.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Designs for new Einstein Museum revealed in Royal Academy Summer Exhibition</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/designs-for-new-einstein-museum-revealed-in-royal-academy-summer-exhibition/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/designs-for-new-einstein-museum-revealed-in-royal-academy-summer-exhibition/</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013</pubDate>
<description>A series of development models for the Einstein Museum at the Mount Scopus Campus of the Hebrew University in Jerusalem will be included in the Royal Academy’s Summer Exhibition in London, which opens on 10 June.</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Application lodged for a new residential quarter in north London</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/application-lodged-for-a-new-residential-quarter-in-north-london/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/application-lodged-for-a-new-residential-quarter-in-north-london/</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013</pubDate>
<description>Plans have been submitted to the London Borough of Islington by Berkeley Homes for the regeneration of a commercial site at 250 City Road, between Angel and Old Street Stations.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Lenbachhaus Museum reopen</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/lenbachhaus-museum-reopens/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/lenbachhaus-museum-reopens/</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013</pubDate>
<description>A ceremony has been held today, attended by German Culture Minister, Mrs Wanka; the Mayor of Munich, Mr Ude; Lord Foster and Dr Helmut Friedl, Director of the Lenbachhaus Museum, to mark the completion of a major project to transform the experience for visitors.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Exhibition: Moving, Norman Foster on Art</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/exhibition-moving-norman-foster-on-art/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/exhibition-moving-norman-foster-on-art/</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013</pubDate>
<description>To mark twenty years since the completion of the Carré d’Art in Nîmes, Norman Foster has been invited to curate a special exhibition to celebrate this anniversary – his design won an international competition for the project in 1984. The title of the exhibition is ‘Moving’ and it brings together 138 works by 66 artists from 14 countries, covering almost a 200 year period from Turner’s early nineteenth-century watercolours to contemporary video pieces.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Three new products launch at Milan Furniture Fair</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/three-new-products-launch-at-milan-furniture-fair/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/three-new-products-launch-at-milan-furniture-fair/</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013</pubDate>
<description></description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Official opening of Queen Alia International Airport in Amman, Jordan</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/official-opening-of-queen-alia-international-airport-in-amman-jordan/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/official-opening-of-queen-alia-international-airport-in-amman-jordan/</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013</pubDate>
<description>Today marked the official opening of Queen Alia International Airport, the spectacular new gateway to Amman. The airport has a highly efficient passive design, which has been inspired by local traditions, and is based on a flexible modular solution that allows for future expansion – the new building secures the city’s position as the main hub for the Levant region and allows the airport to grow by 6 per cent per annum for the next twenty-five years, increasing capacity from 3.5 million to 12 million passengers per annum by 2030.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Planning granted for landmark mixed-use scheme on London's Albert Embankment</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/planning-granted-for-landmark-mixed-use-scheme-on-londons-albert-embankment/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/planning-granted-for-landmark-mixed-use-scheme-on-londons-albert-embankment/</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 </pubDate>
<description>Lambeth Council has approved plans for St James Group’s new mixed-use scheme at 20-21 Albert Embankment in London. Consent was granted for three landmark buildings designed by Foster + Partners, ranging from 15 to 27 storeys in height and providing 253 apartments, including affordable homes for senior living, along with offices, restaurants and a residents’ bar, gym, pool and spa.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foster + Partners exhibition opens in Kuala Lumpur</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-exhibition-opens-in-kuala-lumpur/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-exhibition-opens-in-kuala-lumpur/</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 </pubDate>
<description>'Foster Partners: the Art of Architecture’ will be staged at Galeri PETRONAS, Kuala Lumpur, from 7 March to 12 May 2013. The exhibition is the first major survey of the studio’s work to be held in South East Asia and follows critically acclaimed recent shows in Hong Kong and Shanghai.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>President of Marseille leads opening celebrations for new Vieux Port pavilion</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/president-of-marseille-leads-opening-celebrations-for-new-vieux-port-pavilion/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/president-of-marseille-leads-opening-celebrations-for-new-vieux-port-pavilion/</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013</pubDate>
<description>The transformation of Marseille’s World Heritage-listed harbour was officially inaugurated on Saturday during a ceremony attended by Eugène Caselli, President of Marseille Provence Métropole and Jean-Claude Gaudin, the Mayor of Marseille. The event marked the completion of the new ‘club nautique’ pavilions and a new sheltered events space on the Quai de la Fraternité at the eastern edge of the port, built to commemorate the city’s year as ‘European Capital of Culture’.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Expression of intent to submit Thames Hub Airport proposal lodged with Airports Commission</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/expression-of-intent-to-submit-thames-hub-airport-proposal-lodged-with-airports-commission/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/expression-of-intent-to-submit-thames-hub-airport-proposal-lodged-with-airports-commission/</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013</pubDate>
<description>Foster + Partners has confirmed to the Airports Commission, the organisation investigating airport capacity in the UK led by Sir Howard Davies, that it intends to submit a proposal to the Commission in July for a new hub airport in the Thames Estuary. The airport is part of the proposed Thames Hub, a unique opportunity for an integrated infrastructure solution to rebalance the economy, stimulate growth and enable the UK to maintain its global hub status.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>ME Hotel opens in London</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/me-hotel-opens-in-london/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/me-hotel-opens-in-london/</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013</pubDate>
<description>The ME Hotel – the first flagship hotel in which everything, from the shell of the building to the bathroom fittings has been designed by Foster + Partners – has opened in London. An elegant fusion of interior and exterior design, the scheme completes the grand sweep of buildings that make up the Aldwych Crescent, repairing the urban grain and restoring a little lost glamour to the heart of the West End.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foster + Partners exhibition to open in Kuala Lumpur next month</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-exhibition-to-open-in-kuala-lumpur-next-month/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-exhibition-to-open-in-kuala-lumpur-next-month/</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013</pubDate>
<description>‘Foster + Partners: the Art of Architecture’ will be staged at Galeri PETRONAS, Kuala Lumpur, from 7 March to 12 May 2013. The exhibition is the first major survey of the studio’s work to be held in South East Asia and follows critically acclaimed recent shows in Hong Kong and Shanghai.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foster + Partners completes first project in Latin America</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-completes-first-project-in-latin-america/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-completes-first-project-in-latin-america/</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013</pubDate>
<description>Foster + Partners has completed its first project in Latin America with the opening of the Faena Aleph Residences in Buenos Aires, Argentina – part of the reinvention of the former docks of Puerto Madero as a dynamic new urban quarter. Drawing on local architectural traditions, its apartments feature vaulted living spaces and deep, sheltered terraces that exploit the wonderful local climate and maximise views towards the city and Rio de la Plata.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foster + Partners works with European Space Agency to 3D print structures on the moon</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-works-with-european-space-agency-to-3d-print-structures-on-the-moon/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-works-with-european-space-agency-to-3d-print-structures-on-the-moon/</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013</pubDate>
<description>Foster + Partners is part of a consortium set up by the ESA to explore the possibilities of 3D printing to construct lunar habitations. Addressing the challenges of transporting materials to the moon, the study is investigating the use of lunar soil, known as regolith, as building matter.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Lenbachhaus Museum to reopen on 8 May</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/lenbachhaus-museum-to-reopen-on-8-may/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/lenbachhaus-museum-to-reopen-on-8-may/</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013</pubDate>
<description>The remodelled Lenbachhaus Museum in Munich is to open to the public on 8 May. The first works of art are now being installed, and a press preview was held last week to reveal progress so far and to introduce Foster + Partners' design, which will transform the experience for visitors.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Porcelanosa unveils new flagship New York showroom</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/porcelanosa-unveils-new-flagship-new-york-showroom/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/porcelanosa-unveils-new-flagship-new-york-showroom/</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013</pubDate>
<description>Porcelanosa today revealed designs for its new flagship showroom in the historic Commodore Criterion building in Midtown Manhattan. The firm purchased the 1,700 square-metre, six-storey building northwest of Madison Square Park at 5th Avenue and Broadway in 2012 and selected Foster + Partners to refurbish the interiors – the project is due to be completed in spring 2014.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Foster + Partners to design major new tyre research and development facility in Korea</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-to-design-major-new-tyre-research-and-development-facility-in-korea/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/foster-+-partners-to-design-major-new-tyre-research-and-development-facility-in-korea/</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013</pubDate>
<description>Building on the practice’s previous expertise in the automotive industry, Foster + Partners has been commissioned by Hankook Tire to design a new 99,175-square-metre research and development facility in the city of Daejeon, South Korea. A signing ceremony was held in Daejeon on 7 January to commemorate the new venture.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>2013 RIBA Norman Foster Travelling Scholarship call for entries</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/2013-riba-norman-foster-travelling-scholarship-call-for-entries/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/2013-riba-norman-foster-travelling-scholarship-call-for-entries/</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013</pubDate>
<description>The 2013 RIBA Norman Foster Travelling Scholarship has launched and is inviting applications from schools of architecture around the world. A £6,000 grant will be awarded to one student by a panel of judges which includes Lord Foster and the President of the RIBA.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Designs for the New York Public Library revealed</title>
<link>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/designs-for-the-new-york-public-library-revealed/</link>
<guid>http://www.fosterandpartners.com/news/designs-for-the-new-york-public-library-revealed/</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012</pubDate>
<description>The New York Public Library today unveiled proposals for the integration of the Circulating Library into its flagship Stephen A. Schwarzman Building on 42nd Street – Lord Foster presented the plans at the launch of the public exhibition.</description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>